samuraimeetups.or.jp 2018-08-30

# Privacy policy

The Nonprofit Organization SAMURAI MEETUPS (“the NPO”) aims at “presenting memorable experiences to foreign visitors to Japan” and shall execute the Privacy Policy for the purpose of handling appropriately the Personal Information the User provides in a Google Form sent to SAMURAI MEETUPS website (“the Website”) in order to participate in Events , and make all NPO members constantly aware of the importance to protect all Personal Information.

Article 1 (Personal Information Collection)

The NPO specifies the purpose of utilization for and collects Personal Information of the Users who join Events through appropriate means.

Article2（Personal Information Management）

The NPO implements necessary and safety means such as setting and operating a security system, establishing a management system and educating the NPO members and manages Personal Information strictly for the purpose of maintaining Personal Information accurate and up to date.

Article 3（Purpose of Utilization）

The NPO utilizes Personal Information only for the following purposes.

（1）Provision of Personal Information to Japanese artisans ”SHOKUNIN” who are in partnership with the NPO.

（2）Information necessary for the proper operation of the NPO.

（3）Distribution of lists with the Users’ names  to the NPO members for the proper execution of events.

（4）Purposes incidental above

Article 4 （Provision of Personal Information to a third party）

The NPO shall not disclose and provide Personal Information to a third party without the prior consent of the Users excluding the following cases.

（1）Cases in which the Users’ prior consent has been obtained.

（2）Cases as prescribed by law

（3）Cases where the disclosure and provision of Personal Information is urgently required for the protection of the life, body, or property of an individual and in which there are difficulties in the acquisition of the User’s consent.

（4）Cases where the disclosure and provision of Personal Information is required for the improvement of the  public health or the promotion of participation of Users and where there are difficulties in the acquisition of the User’s consent.

（5）Cases where the handling of Personal Information is necessary for the cooperation with a state organ, a local government, or an individual or a business operator entrusted by either of the former two to execute the affairs prescribed by laws and regulations and where obtaining the User’s  consent is likely to impede the execution of the affairs concerned.

Article 5（Inquiry by a User）

In case a User inquires about or requests his/her Personal Information to be deleted, the NPO verifies the identity of the requester before fulfilling the request.

Article 6（Discontinuance of Utilization, etc.）

Where the NPO is requested by a User to discontinue utilizing or to erase retained Personal Information(“Discontinuance of Utilization”) on the ground that the NPO is handling Personal Information beyond the utilization purpose or acquiring Personal Information by wrongful means, the NPO makes a necessary investigation without delay for the achievement of Discontinuance of Utilization on the basis of the results and informs the User.

Article 7（Change of Privacy Policy）

The NPO can change this Privacy Policy without prior announcement. The new Privacy Policy becomes effective upon its publishing on the NPO’s Website except otherwise provided.

第8条（Inquiry Counter）

In case a User desires to inquire about the Privacy Policy, the User shall contact the Inquiry Counter below.

Nonprofit Organization SAMURAI MEETUPS

〒 104-0061

SAGAMI Building 2nd floor,

7-13-6 Ginza, Chuo ward, Tokyo

samuraimeetups@gmail.com
